[Music]
oh man Anya this festival is going to be
bitchin I can't wait for your brothers
Sonic and Manic to get here with their
berries I'm starving like a pixie
ha ha I know what you mean Knuckles I
hope they get here soon the sooner they
get here the sooner the grand Pixie
Festival can start hey guys sorry I'm
late
Manic will also be here soon man Sonic
what took you so long
did some tree sap fall on your wings
again causing you to walk all the way
here on foot
actually what took me so long to get
here once this fine beauty right here
holy pixie do my pixie eyes deceive
me or are those fresh moon drop cherries
from the eastern mountains they sure are
my pixie friend we are going to dine
like pixie kings and queens at this
grand festival sub 6 Oh Manik you've
arrived top row now that you're here
Manik we can finally start the grand
Pixie Festival cool let's make this a
party we'll never forget hold up guys
remember before we chow down we must do
the pixie prayer that we say every year
at this fine event oh I almost forgot
our prayer to God Taymor's 1 2 3 4 5 the
great pixie in the sky to make sure that
we make it safely through the upcoming
winter
Knuckles how about you start us off
don't mind if I do my pixie
oh great Amer's 1 2 3 4 5 though we
Pixies are only 5 feet tall to survive
the winter ahead we will give it our all
we scavenge the forest looking for as
much food as we can get while making
sure not to be seen by humans and caught
in a net if we don't get enough food for
the winter the pixie rays could die but
we won't let that happen
because if it did we would cry so help
us survive this winter so that once
spring comes we can have a blast help us
survive and kick the winters
amen all right now that that's out of
the way let's eat everyone
[Music]
what is this everything turned all cold
and Wendy all of a sudden this is oh my
God it's a blizzard a blizzard
but that means everything we've gathered
to prepare for the window from the food
to the clothes will be destroyed oh my
God look at all the other Pixies they're
screaming in terror not only that but
the cold winter air is turning them into
Pixy icicles
[Applause]
this this is so horrible the winter came
early this year the festival has been
ruined we're all going to die this this
is
Knuckles calm down now I won't calm down
this happens every year every
year we throw this damn festival -
laughs - cheer but all that ends up
doing is raining depression that and
literally I'm done with it
100% done with this you can be done
with it
but first shouldn't we all work together
to go and rescue the rest of the Pixies
of the Eastern woods I guess you are
right but we can't do it alone
we need a search party if we want to
rescue as much people as possible let's
call the rest of the gang here at once
hint
you
sup sugar tits try not to overdo it out
there the blizzard is really fierce TV
you don't have to tell me twice baby
I've got this
sup mama mother you're here thank God
I'm so scared
oh don't worry Sonia I'm here to protect
you sweetie
I'll reach children let's get down to
business and kick this blizzard sauce
you got it Uncle Chuck